Guide to the H. Boone Porter Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Biographical Documentation, 1958-1999; Series IX
  - Personal materials
    - HBP's memorabilia: miscellaneous, no date (Box 76, Folder 784)
    - Re. death of HBP: obituaries, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 785)
    - Re. death of HBP: funeral materials, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 786)
    - Re. death of HBP: condolence letters, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 787)
    - Re. death of HBP: tributes and memorials, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 788)
      See also Bishop F. Putnam's memorial cassette in Series X, box 84, folder 867.
  - Porter family materials
    - Heritage: Daniel Boone information, no date (Box 77, Folder 789)
    - News items and publications, 1985-1999 (Box 77, Folder 790)
    - Cemetery lot, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 791)
    - Nicolas Porter's Ordination, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 792)
  - Personal calendars
    - Daily, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 793-794)
    - Monthly, 1971-1998 (Box 78, Folder 795-800)
  - Non-professional affiliations
    - Alumni Association of St. Paul's School, 1968-1996 (Box 79, Folder 801)
    - Audobon Society, 1985-1986 (Box 79, Folder 802)
    - Berkeley Divinity School, 1994-1995 (Box 79, Folder 803)
    - Cuttyhunk Yacht Club, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 804)
    - Elizabethan Club of Yale University, 1991-1996 (Box 79, Folder 805)
    - Henry Bradshaw Society, 1979-1990 (Box 79, Folder 806)
    - Nashotah House Alumni Association, 1978-1991 (Box 79, Folder 807)
    - Penndennis Club, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 808)
    - Pequot Yacht Club, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 809)
    - Philadelphia Society, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 810)
    - Sea Lodge, 1991-1997 (Box 79, Folder 811)
    - Yale Club, 1969-1995 (Box 79, Folder 812)
  - Miscellaneous conferences/events
    Organized chronologically
    - Gallican Liturgy demonstration, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 813)
      See the corresponding photographs in Series X, box 83, folder 865.
    - Professors of Mission Conference: summary of proceedings, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 814)
    - Sagada Liturgical Conference: notes and schedule, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 815)
    - Liturgical Renewal Conference: general records, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 816)
    - "In His Hands" radio series: general records, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 817)
    - Rochester Clergy Conference: general records, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 818)
    - Chaplains Conference: program, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 819)
    - General Convention: "Green Book", 1969 (Box 80, Folder 820-821)
    - General Convention: general records and constitution amendment proposal, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 822)
    - Society of the Companions of the Holy Cross retreat: general records, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 823)
    - Quincy-Springfield Retreat: general records, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 824)
    - Ordination of Arthur Vogel: general records, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 825)
    - Valparaiso Institute lecture: general records, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 826)
    - Central American Theological Education: correspondence, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 827)
    - Notre Dame Liturgical Conference: HBP's paper and correspondence, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 828)
    - Theological Education by Extension workshop: general records, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 829)
    - Consecration of David Cochran: HBP's sermon, ceremony program, etc., 1974 (Box 81, Folder 830)
    - Soil Stewardship Week: HBP's articles, correspondence, etc., 1974-1977 (Box 81, Folder 831-832)
    - College of Preachers Liturgy Conference: general records, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 833)
    - Convention of the Diocese of West Missouri: HBP's talks, schedule, etc., 1976 (Box 81, Folder 834)
    - Florida Diocesan Clergy Retreat: HBP's notes and correspondence, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 835)
    - General Convention: "Blue Book", constitution amendment proposal, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 836-839)
    - Nevada Diaconate Symposium, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 840)
    - National Association of Diocesan Altar Guilds conference: HBP's talk and correspondence, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 841)
    - Midwest Patristics Seminar: correspondence, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 842)
    - Clergy and Wives R&R: HBP's notes, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 843)
    - Nashotah House Sheridan Lecture: HBP's talk and correspondence, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 844)
    - "Advancing Anglican Catholicity" conference: general records, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 845)
    - Book of Common Prayer course in Norwalk: HBP's notes, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 846)
    - Holy Cross lecture: HBP's talk and correspondence, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 847)
    - "Richard Hooker: Celebration and Appraisal" event: general records, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 848)
    - Holy Cross Retreat: HBP's lecture notes, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 849)
    - Anglican Orders Conference: HBP's talks and correspondence, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 850)
    - C.C.U. talk: HBP's notes, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 851)
    - Yale 50th Reunion: general records, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 852)
    - Hie Hill Symposium: correspondence, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 853)
- Audio-Visual Materials, 1950s-1999; Series X
  - Photographs
    - Portraits of HBP, 1950s-1990s (Box 83, Folder 854)
    - Gallican Liturgy demonstration, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 855)
    - Round the world trip, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 856)
    - LAND at Roanridge, 1975-1977 (Box 83, Folder 857)
    - LAND at Roanridge, 1975-1977 (Box 83, Folder 858)
    - The Living Church, 1980s (Box 83, Folder 859)
    - Jerusalem Interim: St. George's College, 1992-1996 (Box 83, Folder 860)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940s-1990s (Box 83, Folder 861)
    - Roland Allen research, 1970s (Box 83, Folder 862)
  - Slides
    - Asia and Alaska trip, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 863)
      Digital versions of the slides are available.
  - Audio materials
    - Cassette: letter, no date (Box 83, Folder 864)
    - Cassette: Kansas LAND history, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 865)
    - Cassettes: ATR On Tape: "The Small/Rural Church", 1996 (Box 84, Folder 866)
    - Cassette: HBP memorial by Bishop F. Putnam, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 867)